♪I lament on the cruel and untimely love♪
أنا أتحسر على الحب القاسي والغير أوانه ♪
♪Yet I come to realise it's a daydream when the bubbles burst♪
♪ ومع ذلك أدركت أنه حلم يقظة عندما تنفجر الفقاعات ♪
♪A city of spring flowers♪
♪ مدينة زهور الربيع ♪
♪Sinks into the indifferent autumnal frost♪
♪ يغرق في الصقيع الخريفي غير المبال
♪A snowflake falls into the river♪
♪ تسقط ندفة ثلجية في النهر ♪
♪The biting cold stalks over♪
♪ السيقان الباردة القارضة
♪All assumptions are nothing♪
كل الافتراضات لا شيء
♪But a disguised makeup♪
♪ لكن مكياج مقنع
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the passionate gaze behind the mask♪
♪ للنظرة العاطفية خلف القناع ♪
♪Love and hate are the most unforgettable feelings♪
الحب والكراهية من أكثر المشاعر التي لا تنسى
♪Overwhelmed by my longings♪
غارقة في شوقي ♪
♪I tear off those old scores♪
♪ مزقت تلك الدرجات القديمة ♪
♪I bid farewell♪
أودع
♪To the irretrievable past♪
إلى الماضي الذي لا يمكن استرجاعه ♪
=Little Mad Doctor=
= الطبيب المجنون الصغير =
=Episode 19=
= الحلقة 19 =
Should I address you as Director Ye
هل يجب أن أخاطبكم بصفتي المدير يي
or
أو
Lord War?
لورد الحرب؟
I wonder what's your identity
أتساءل ما هي هويتك
in the capital.
في العاصمة.
Should I call you Master Hua
هل يجب أن أدعوك سيد هوا
or the Crown Prince?
أو ولي العهد؟
As expected from the most sensitive intelligence agency of Shang.
كما هو متوقع من وكالة الاستخبارات الأكثر حساسية في شانغ.
Today,
اليوم،
I came here for one thing.
جئت إلى هنا من أجل شيء واحد.
Please let Chu Jinghong go.
من فضلك دع تشو جينغهونغ يذهب.
Don't take her as your wife
لا تأخذها كزوجة لك
or mess up with her.
أو العبث معها.
As for people and state
أما الشعب والدولة
she wants to protect,
تريد أن تحمي ،
as her brother,
كأخيها ،
I will fulfil her wishes.
سأفي برغباتها.
Why did you say so?
لماذا قلت ذلك؟
Needless to say,
لا داعي لقوله،
people who hold different stances and motives
الناس الذين لديهم مواقف ودوافع مختلفة
shouldn't be shoved together.
لا ينبغي دفعها معًا.
Lord War, you're scheming
يا رب الحرب ، أنت مكيدة
and all you do is for your own sake.
وكل ما تفعله هو مصلحتك.
You never
انت ابدا
hold her dearly.
امسكها غاليا.
How can you be sure
كيف يمكنك ان تكون متأكدا
that I don't?
لا أفعل؟
Since you've learnt of my identity,
منذ أن علمت بهويتي ،
you should know that everything I did
يجب أن تعلم أن كل ما فعلته
is for the sake of my sister.
هو من اجل اختي.
You should consider this well.
يجب أن تفكر في هذا جيدًا.
How do I know
كيف أعرف
what you're after?
ماذا بعد
The thing is
الشيء هو
if you don't hurt her,
إذا لم تؤذيها ،
I won't attack you
لن أهاجمك
no matter who you are.
لا يهم من انت.
Likewise,
على نفس المنوال،
if you were to hurt her,
إذا كنت ستؤذيها ،
I won't let you off the hook
لن أتركك خارج الخطاف
no matter who you are.
لا يهم من انت.
Interesting.
مثير للاهتمام.
Very interesting.
مثير جدا.
Scram.
انصرف.
Don't you cling to Second Prince.
لا تتشبث بالأمير الثاني.
Get out of here.
اخرج من هنا.
Please pass this to His Highness.
يرجى تمرير هذا إلى صاحب السمو.
Leave right now.
غادر حالا.
(Lord War's Residence)
(مقر اللورد وورز)
Apologies, Miss Jin'er.
أعتذر يا آنسة جينير.
Without Lord War's order,
بدون أمر Lord War ،
you're not allowed to enter.
لا يسمح لك بالدخول.
(Lord War's Residence)
(مقر اللورد وورز)
Look at your pitiful face.
انظر إلى وجهك المثير للشفقة.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
I shall offer you some food.
سأقدم لك بعض الطعام.
Don't forget you're pregnant now.
لا تنسي أنك حامل الآن.
If you don't eat,
إذا كنت لا تأكل ،
your baby will suffer.
سوف يعاني طفلك.
I don't intend to save you.
لا أنوي إنقاذك.
But I'm a merciful woman.
لكن أنا امرأة رحيمة.
Why did you save her, Your Highness?
لماذا أنقذتها يا صاحب السمو؟
I'm afraid Second Prince will be upset.
أخشى أن يكون الأمير الثاني مستاء.
No, I never wanted to save her.
لا ، لم أرغب أبدًا في إنقاذها.
A lowly maidservant
خادمة وضيعة
just doesn't deserve
فقط لا يستحق
to give birth to royal descent.
لتلد سلالة ملكية.
Then...
ثم...
Why have you done this?
لماذا فعلت هذا؟
Today is the first day of the new year.
اليوم هو أول أيام العام الجديد.
I'm going to prepare a present
سأقوم بإعداد هدية
for Chu Jinghong.
من أجل Chu Jinghong.
Why hasn't His Highness back yet? We're waiting for the meal.
لماذا لم يعد سموه بعد؟  نحن ننتظر الوجبة.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Chunyu came here. The maidservant of Wen Liangyu.
جاء Chunyu إلى هنا ، خادمة Wen Liangyu.
Greetings, Princess Jinghong.
تحياتي ، الأميرة جينغهونغ.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
This is a present from Princess Liangyu.
هذه هدية من الأميرة ليانغيو.
A present from Wen Liangyu?
هدية من Wen Liangyu؟
It must be something grim.
يجب أن يكون شيئًا قاتمًا.
I won't accept this.
لن أقبل هذا.
Bring it back.
أعدها.
Princess Jinghong.
الأميرة جينغهونغ.
Her Highness said
قالت سموها
if you don't accept this,
إذا كنت لا تقبل هذا ،
I can't be back alive.
لا أستطيع أن أعود على قيد الحياة.
Jin'er.
جينير.
I made this ring.
لقد صنعت هذا الخاتم.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
Sure there is.
بالتأكيد هناك.
These are our best friend rings,
هذه هي أفضل حلقات الأصدقاء لدينا ،
representing our friendship.
تمثل صداقتنا.
Jin'er.
جينير.
Jin'er is with you.
جينير معك.
Her Highness said
قالت سموها
that if you're curious about the answer,
أنه إذا كنت مهتمًا بالإجابة ،
find it in Suoqing Palace.
تجده في Suoqing Palace.
What dirty trick she's doing again?
ما الحيلة القذرة التي تقوم بها مرة أخرى؟
Jin'er has betrayed me.
لقد خانني جينير.
Her life
حياتها
doesn't concern me.
لا تقلقني.
If you don't go,
إذا لم تذهب ،
Her Highness will assign me to send one gift here every day
ستخصص لي سموها هدية واحدة هنا كل يوم
until Jin'er...
حتى جينير ...
Enough.
كافٍ.
Fine, I will go.
حسنا سأذهب.
She's being so cruel to a pregnant woman.
إنها قاسية جدًا على امرأة حامل.
I will punish her
سوف أعاقبها
in the name of justice.
باسم العدالة.
Sese.
خطأ.
Inform Yu Longyuan
أبلغ يو لونجيوان
to go to Suoqing Palace.
للذهاب إلى قصر Suoqing.
Yes.
نعم.
Jinghong.
جينغهونغ.
Wen Liangyu's target has always been you.
لطالما كان هدف Wen Liangyu هو أنت.
She must be harboring an evil intention
يجب أن يكون لديها نية شريرة
to lure you there.
لجذبك هناك.
Jin'er.
جينير.
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد
♪Hair turns grey in one winter night♪
♪ يتحول لون الشعر إلى اللون الرمادي في ليلة شتاء ♪
♪The appearance remains in spite of the thick frost♪
المظهر يبقى بالرغم من الصقيع الكثيف
♪Time slips by in that dream-like world♪
♪ الوقت يمر في هذا العالم الذي يشبه الحلم
♪Life is always full of splendor♪
♪ الحياة دائما مليئة بالروعة
♪We part when the flowers fall♪
♪ نفترق عندما تسقط الأزهار
♪Desolate chills blow away several autumns♪
♪ قشعريرة مقفرة تهب عدة خريفات ♪
♪Eternal love is all I seek♪
الحب الأبدي هو كل ما أسعى إليه
♪Though the sweet dream fades at last♪
رغم أن الحلم الجميل يتلاشى أخيرًا ♪
♪I sigh at my life♪
♪ أنا أتنهد في حياتي ♪
♪There's nowhere to anchor on shore♪
♪ لا يوجد مكان للرسو على الشاطئ
♪Nothing to cherish in the world♪
لا شيء نعتز به في العالم
♪Except for you♪
ما عداك ♪
♪The past we've been through retains♪
♪ الماضي الذي مررنا به
♪Even though time wears thin♪
على الرغم من أن الوقت يضعف ♪
♪The thought of being together lifelong♪
فكرة البقاء معًا مدى الحياة
♪Exists beyond time♪
موجود خارج الزمن ♪
♪All joys and sorrows♪
♪ كل افراح و احزان ♪
♪Reflect in your gentle gaze♪
انعكس في نظراتك اللطيفة
♪I will spend my life waiting♪
♪ سأقضي حياتي في الانتظار ♪
♪For the chance to be forever by your side♪
للحصول على فرصة أن تكون بجانبك إلى الأبد